HYEYOUNG (JANE) BYUN

Phone: (647)785 4564

Email: byun.hyeyoung@gmail.com

Summary

Result oriented, ambitious and resourceful individual with 5 years of experience in strategic marketing, business development, project planning and execution to drive business and engage clients. 5+ year experience with market research, target market identification, traditional and digital marketing, content marketing, seller buyer relationship, persuasive communication and negotiations.

Work Experience

SENIOR PROJECT MANAGER - LPR Global Inc - Toronto, Canada

Jan 2021 - Present

- Oversee 6 projects as an acting program manager and suggest strategic solutions to rising problems and risks.
- Overhaul and improve relationships between consulting clients and their clients including meeting facilitation, conflict resolution and problem solving during the contractual period.
- Expedite overseas sourcing services including research and qualification of new vendors, technical specification discussion, and project term negotiations.

PROJECT MANAGER - LPR Global Inc - Toronto, Canada

May 2015 - Dec 2020

- Consulted 4 contract clients in Manufacturing, Steel, and Automotive industries simultaneously and successfully met or exceeded client deliverables in marketing and B2B business development.
- Managed 10 brand and product portfolios by developing customized marketing plans and tailored marketing messages for each product portfolio based on analysis of meetings with prospects including Fortune 100 companies.
- Executed marketing and communication plans through calling campaigns, digital marketing, webpage development, tradeshow, factory visits and marketing presentations with potential buyers and partners.
- Created and revised web content and optimized SEO to increase unique visitors by 200% and online inquiries by 150% in a year.
- Posted and maintained company blog posts by revising and tightening blog contents to engage prospects, and optimize the blog content and keywords for both audience and search engines.
- Developed business leads and gather primary market research, involving 6-7 business travels annually to USA, UK, Poland, Russia and S.Korea through more than 10 international trade shows and conferences, and more than 50 1-on-1 meetings with global buyers as a representative of clients.
- Increased client retention rate by 90% through outstanding client management, strategic marketing, and development of global projects opportunities.

Skills

- Project Management PMP certified, 5 years experience managing up to 6 marketing & brand development projects a year
- Research Skills Market research, prospect or vendor research and qualification analysis
- Meeting Facilitation and Negotiation Skills Technical specification discussions, and negotiations on sales & purchase terms
- Proficient in SEO (Search Engine Optimization) using Google Analytics and Google Console and creating compelling content
- Competent in website content creation using wordpress and HTML
- Familiar with Salesforce, Husbpot and CRM programs, and able to utilize them without training
- Critical thinker, able to make decisions with limited information,
- Excellent communication skills, persuasive communication, and generating solutions to resolve problems under pressure
- Microsoft Office Word, Powerpoint, Excel, and Outlook

Education

HONOURS BACHELOR OF SCIENCE – University of Toronto, St. George Campus Graduated with High Honours Distinction | Dean's List – 4 years

2011-2015

- University of Toronto Scholars Program Scholarship
- Trinity College Chancellor's Scholarship from the Ashbaugh fund
- Market Researcher and Analyst at student formed market research organization Analyst Outsourcing Unit
- Summer and ROP Research Student at The Mount Sinai Hospital's Placental Capillarization Research led by Professor Lee. Adamson

OPERATIONS AND SUPPLY CHAIN MANAGEMENT — University of Toronto School of Continuing Studies

Dec. 2020

• Operations and Supply Chain Management (OSCM), Parameters of a sustainable supply chain strategy, Total quality management, Six sigma quality concept, Forecasting, Capacity management, Logistics and facilities layout tools and techniques